Guide to the Foundation for Theological Education in South East Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Administrative Records, 1937-2010; Series I
  - H. S. Wilson era
    - Executive Committee meeting, annual meeting, directory, 2008 Dec (Box 38, Folder 355)
    - Executive Committee meeting, incl. guidelines for scholarship funds, guidelines for program grants, guidelines for nominations, 2009 Jun (Box 38, Folder 356)
    - Executive Committee meeting, annual meeting, directory, 2009 Dec (Box 38, Folder 357)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 2010 Jun (Box 38, Folder 358)
    - 75th Anniversary working group meeting, Executive Committee meeting, annual meeting, 2010 Oct (Box 38, Folder 359)
    - FTESEA website printout, 2011 Feb (Box 38, Folder 360)
- Financial Records, FTE, 1980-2009; Series II
  - Tax records, 1980-1986 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Requests to pay, 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 126-129)
  - Audited financial statements, 1983-2009 (Box 31, Folder 297- 303)
- Audio-visual Materials, ca. 1974-2010; Series III
  - Photos of FTESEA meetings and people, ca. 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 130)
  - Photos of opening of unidentified seminary, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 304)
  - Photos of FTESEA Executive Committee visit to China, 2002 May (Box 32, Folder 305-310)
  - Photos from visit of Gerald Anderson, Marvin D. Hoff and Ben Chan to Nanjing and Shanghai, incl. with Bishop K. H. Ting, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 349)
  - Photos of opening of FTESEA office in Mangalore, India; printout of "Photos" section of FTESEA website as of 12-31-2010, 2007-2010 (Box 32, Folder 311)
  - CD: "Protestant Churches in China", 2003 (Box 32, Folder 312)
  - DVD: "'A Lamp to my feet, A Light to my path': Bible Ministry of the Protestant Churches in China", ca. 2006 (Box 32, Folder 313)
- ATSSEA/ ATESEA Resources, 1958-2009; Series IV
  - Thailand theological seminary newsletter: Herald, 1969-1976 (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Bangkok Institute of Theology Bulletin, 1970s? (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Singapore - Trinity Theological College, Board of Governors meeting and catalogue, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - Singapore - Trinity Theological College newsletter: Trumpet, 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - Philippines - reports from St. Andrews and other misc documents, probably from St. Andrews, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - Philippines - Union Theological Seminary report, pamphlet and catalogue, 1960-1961, 1965, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 137)
  - Philippines - various seminary brochures, including: 7th Day Adventist; Lutheran Theological Seminary; Baptist Seminary; Harris Memorial College, mid 1970s (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - Philippines - newsletter of the College of Theology, Central Philippines University: Shalom, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - Philippines - Silliman University catalogue and pamphlets, mid 1970s (Box 14, Folder 140)
  - Malaysia - Methodist Theological School, brochures and report, 1962-1976 (Box 14, Folder 141)
  - Malaysia - Singapore Baptist Theological Seminary catalogue, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 142)
  - Taiwan - various seminary documents including:Yu Shan Theological Institute; Hsinchu Presbyterian Bible School; Tainan Theological College; Taiwan Theological College, mid 1970s (Box 14, Folder 143)
  - Indonesia - Reports on theological schools from Elmer Douglas (1968) and Robbins Strong (1977); Satya Wacna University; Duta Wacna United Theological College, 1968,1977,1974,1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 144)
  - Hong Kong - various seminary documents including: China Graduate School of Theology; Concordia Seminary; Chung Chi College and others, 1974-1978 (Box 14, Folder 145)
  - Burma Divinity School, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 146)
  - ATSSEA Handbooks, 1978-79 (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - ATSSEA Handbooks, 1980-81 (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - ATSSEA Source Book, member schools, 1975-78 (Box 15, Folder 149)
  - Minutes, 1967-1979 (Box 15, Folder 150-159)
  - Reports, minutes, papers, 1971-1993 (Box 33, Folder 314-317)
  - Hsin Chu Lay Training Center meeting, 1992 Oct (Box 33, Folder 318-319)
  - Correspondence of Rev. Yeow Choo Lak, 1994-2002 (Box 33, Folder 320-321)
  - Accreditation Commission meeting, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 322)
  - Management and leadership workshop report (Box 33, Folder 323)
  - Miscellaneous ATSSEA / ATESEA reportsand publications, 1968-1973 (Box 36, Folder 331)
  - ATESEA Golden Jubilee Handbook 1957-2007; ATESEA Handbook 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 332)
  - ATESEA Taskforce Research Report on the Future, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 333)
- Publications, 1956-2010; Series V
  - Books for China / South East Asia
    - Books in 1st series of the Christian Classics Library Nos. 2,4,8,14,15,16, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - Books in the 2nd series of the Christian Classics Library, published in Chinese: #3 Selected Works of Martin Luther Vol 2, (1959) trans C. Tang, Martin Yang, Clayton Chu, Ching You Hsu, S. Y. Dai, I. Tang; #5 Institutes of the Christian Religion, Vol 2 by John Calvin (1964) trans Ching-yu Hsu, Ping-teh Hsieh; #8 Quaker Classics, Selections from George Fox, John Wollman, and Robert Barclay, trans. Moses Hsu; #9 The Anglican Thought (1972), trans N. Z. Zia, C. W. Wu; #10 British Presbyterianism and Puritanism, trans. M. Hsu, C. S. Chao, and others; #21 The Social Gospel of Rauschenbusch (1956), trans Chao Chen-Sung., 1956-1972 (Box 17, Folder 161)
    - Books in Chinese with untranslated titles, probably in the Christian Classics Library:Troelsch, social teachings; philosophy of Descartes, Locke, Tindal, Butler, Hume, and Kant (Box 18, Folder 162)
    - A Preliminary and Tentative Listing of Books for the Libraries of Christian Theological Institutions in South-East Asia, compiled for the Nanking Board of Founders by Raymond P. Morris, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 164)
  - Periodicals
    - The Chinese Theological Review, 1985-1991 (Box 19, Folder 164)
    - The Chinese Theological Review, 1992-2000 (Box 20, Folder 165)
    - The Chinese Theological Review, Vols. 16, 18, 19, 20, 21, 2002-2008 (Box 34, Folder 324)
    - The Chinese Theological Review Vol. 17, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 192)
    - Nanjing Theological Review, 2004-2008 (Box 34, Folder 325)
  - FTESEA history
    - "History of Nanking Theological Seminary 1911 to 1961" by Frank Wilson Price (Box 37, Folder 341)
    - A River of Living Water, a historical sketch of the Nanking Theological Seminary, Nanking, China, and The Board of Founders, by Frank Cartwright., 1963 (Box 18, Folder 163)
    - Proposals for FTE history, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 196-197)
    - Partnership in Training God's Servants for Asia: Essays in Honor of Marvin D. Hoff, ed. by Sientje Merentek-Abram and A. Wati Longchar, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 326)
    - Chinese Theological Education, 1979-2006, ed. by Marvin D. Hoff (Grand Rapids, Mich.: William B. Eerdmans Pub. Co., 2009) (Box 35, Folder 327)
    - Supporting Asian Christianity's Transition from Mission to Church: a history of the Foundation for Theological Education in South East Asia, ed. by Samuel C. Pearson (Grand Rapids, Mich.: Wm. B. Eerdmans Pub. Co., c2010) (Box 35, Folder 328)
    - Typescript manuscripts for FTESEA history (Box 37, Folder 342-346)
  - Related to FTESEA partners
    - Books by Bishop K.H. Ting: Love Never Ends and God is Love, 2000, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 329)
    - Booklet: "New York Visit of the Delegation from the Three-Self Patriotic Movement and the China Christian Council", 2003 Oct (Box 35, Folder 330)
    - Booklet: "Protestant Churches in China", ca. 2004 (Box 37, Folder 347)
    - WCC / Ecumenical Theological Education publications: "Ministerial Formation 110: Jubilee Issue"; "Challenges and Opportunities for Theological Education in the 21st Century", 2008, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 348)